-Good! You guys are all here.
-What's up?
다들 여기 있었구나
왔니? 무슨 일인데?
나 내일 랄프 로렌에
면접 보러 가
I have a job interview
at Ralph Lauren tomorrow.
- 축하해
- 잘됐다
Congratulations!
Oh, boy.
That guy's underwear sucks!
그 친구 속옷 개판인데
-What?
-Well, I got this pair marked "XS."
뭐?
XS 사이즈래서 샀는데
자꾸 기어 나와서
입을 수가 없더라고
Let me tell you, there was no room
for excess anything in there.
I'll be the coordinator
of the women's collection.
어쨌든 잘되면 이사 밑에서
코디네이터로 일할 수 있어
I'll work right under the director.
It's the perfect job for me!
너무 완벽한 자리야
If you nail the interview,
you'll get it.
인터뷰만 통과하면
확정이란 말이지?
그래
You want to work
on your interview skills?
인터뷰 연습할래?
- 좋아
- 그래
Let's start with the handshake.
우선 악수부터 하자
- 반가워요
- 안녕하세요
Very good handshake.
Good wrist action.
아주 좋아요
손목도 부드럽고
감사합니다
- 나도 해볼래
- 그래
Let me try.
아야! 얘 사람 잡겠네
Oh, my God!
What did I ever do to you?
Did I squeeze too hard?
너무 꽉 쥐었니?
내가 챈들러가 아니라
천만다행이다
Let's just say
I'm glad I'm not Chandler.
The One with Rachel's lnadvertent Kiss
그래, 로스, 너 아주 잘 보여
너도 나 보이지?
That's right, Ross.
I can see you in your new apartment.
Same as yesterday,
same as the day before.
어제도 그랬고
그 전날도 그랬지
Is he doing
his "shark attack" bit?
- 상어의 공격은 시작됐나?
- 아니...
No. Oh, wait!
There he goes.
잠깐, 지금 한다
진짜 웃긴다, 로스
Very funny, Ross.
실감나고 웃겨, 그래
Very lifelike and funny.
No, no.
I wasn't waving at you, lady.
아뇨, 아가씨한테
손 흔든 거 아니에요
Whoa, maybe I was.
와, 못 흔들 것도 없지 뭐
모니카, 죽이는 여자가
날 보고 생글거리는데?
This hot girl in Ross' building
is flirting with me.
박자 맞춰 줘
마구 엉키는 거야
Get in there, man.
Flirt back. Mix it up!
지금 누굴 가르쳐?
Yeah, I'm down with that.
Okay, here goes.
좋았어
How...
안...
...you...
녕...
...doing?
하쇼!
It worked! She's waving me over.
I'll be right over.
먹혀들었어
나한테 손짓한다
지금 그쪽으로 갈게요
어디 보자, 3층이고...
Let's see,
she's on the third floor....
와! 정말 예쁜데
-She is pretty, huh?
-Tell me about it.
두말하면 잔소리
아... 아뇨!
No, no! I'm not with her.
나랑 상관없는 애예요
얜 그냥 모니카라구요
That's just Monica.
우엑!
Hey, Joey!
너냐, 조이?
Great stuff, huh?
멋진 쇼였지?
This your place?
여기가 너희 집이냐?
당연하지, 어서 들어와
Yeah, of course it is.
Come on in.
너도 창가에 서봐
파도타기도 할 수 있어
Go by the window.
You can pretend to be surfing.
I counted.
You're not supposed to live here!
분명히 제대로 셌는데
쟤가 왜 여기 있지?
돌겠네
Oh, man!
What happened?
어떻게 됐어?
가니까 로스 집이잖아
잘못 셌나 봐
I ended up at Ross' place.
I must have miscounted or something.
Damn! She's not there anymore.
망할, 이젠 없잖아
Look, Ross is doing
his "watching TV" bit.
저것 봐, 이번엔
TV 시청 편이다
No, Joe, I think
he's just watching TV.
진짜로 보는 것 같은데?
We've lost visual contact
with the suspect.
용의자를 놓쳤다
Okay, now I really have to go.
이젠 정말 가야겠어
It's so unfair that
our date has to get cut short...
점원한테 총질한 녀석 때문에
헤어져야 하다니 분통 터져
...just because some guy
shot at a store clerk.
내 직업인 걸 어떡해
-I know, but it's my job.
-Then maybe I could come too.
나도 따라가면 안 돼?
Suspect has just emerged
naked from the sewer.
방금 용의자가 하수구에서
알몸으로 나타났다
All right, you go.
됐어, 가봐
- 안녕
- 그래
잘 가
-Oh, God!
-What?
- 이런!
- 왜?
개리가 너무 보고 싶다
Oh, I just miss him so much!
For just a week,
you guys are close.
- 일주일만에 그렇게 됐어?
- 그래, 이상하지?
Yeah, it's weird.
I can't help it. He's so sweet.
하지만 너무 귀여운 걸 어떡해
꼭 강아지 같다니까
He's like this little
puppy dog, you know?
악당한테 총알 먹이는
엄청 터프한 강아지
But like a really tough one
who shoots bad guys.
I love the beginning parts
of relationships.
이럴 때가 제일 가슴 떨려
You can't keep your hands
off each other.
- 잠시도 떨어져있기 싫고
- 알아, 좋은 때지
I know. It is the best.
너랑 챈들러는 언제까지 그랬어?
How long did that last
for you and Chandler?
What? It's still going on.
뭐가?
우린 아직도 그래
Come on, seriously.
When did it end?
농담하지 말고
언제 끝났니?
I am serious. We're all over
each other all the time.
농담하는 거 아냐
지금도 서로를 간절히 원해
Okay, you know where you are
better than I do.
그래, 네가 더 잘 알겠지
그냥 궁금해서 물어봤어
제발 이성을 찾아라
Why don't you just calm down?
Get all your facts before you tell
everybody you're the only hot couple.
너희만 세상에서 유일하게
뜨거운 커플인 줄 알아?
God, I woke the beast.
잠자는 괴수를 깨웠군
I was wrong, obviously.
I just misspoke. It's okay.
그래, 내가 말을 잘못했어
인정할게
당연하지
It is okay.
As long as you know Chandler and l
are also hot and fiery.
나랑 챈들러도 너희 못지 않게
뜨거운 사이라는 것만 알아둬
Just as hot as you.
우리의 불길은...
I mean, our flame....
It is on fire!
휴! 걷잡을 수가 없어
모니카, 너희 빗자루야
Here's your broom back.
You are so cute!
너무 근사한 내 남자!
The cute bar keeps getting lower
and lower, doesn't it?
근사한 남자 점점
주가 떨어지는데?
왔구나, 인터뷰 어떻게 됐어?
How'd the interview go?
끔찍했어
창피해서 얼굴을 못 들겠네
Horrible! I did the stupidest,
most embarrassing thing.
면접관 부인이랑 자겠다고
하면서 의자에서 떨어졌냐?
Did you say you wanted to have sex
with his wife then fall off your chair?
아니
Did you get drunk on the way over there?
가면서 술 마셨니?
아니
Well, that explains why you didn't do
the other stuff.
그래서 그 짓을 못했구나
So, what happened?
무슨 일인데?
정말 죽고 싶다
인터뷰는 잘됐지
It was horrible!
And the interview part went so well.
면접관도 웃기고
I even made him laugh.
보트 얘기를 꺼내서
내가 그랬거든
He said something about a boat...
...and I was like, "Well, yeah,
if you've got enough life jackets."
'네, 구명조끼만 충분하다면'
아무튼 무지 웃긴 얘기였어
Trust me.
It was actually very funny.
어쨌거나...
그렇게 끝이 나고...
Anyway, we were
saying goodbye and....
What happened?
어떻게 됐어?
We were shaking hands...
악수를 하는데...
...and he leaned in toward me.
내게 몸을 숙이는 거야
Maybe he was opening the door...
문을 열어주려고 한 모양인데
난 그런 줄도 모르고 그만...
...but I totally
misread him and I....
키스를 했어?
You kissed him?
달리 어떻게 할 방법이 없었어
I didn't know what else to do!
You could have tried...
그런 경우엔...
키스를 안 해야지
...not kissing him.
Thanks, Chandler.
고맙다, 챈들러
A guy from Ralph Lauren called.
You got a second interview.
레이첼
랄프 로렌에서 연락 왔는데
2차 면접 보러 오래
Monica, that's not funny.
하나도 안 웃겨
Oh, okay.
알았어
A guy from Ralph Lauren called
You got a second interview
랄프 로렌 전화했네
2차 면접 있다하네
Oh, my God, Monica,
you better be serious.
지금 장난하는 거 아니지?
You just told me to be funny!
웃기게 하라며
이럴 수가...
Oh, my God. I can't believe it!
I got a second interview.
- 내가 1차에 붙었어?
- 그래
이제 보니 그 키스가
꼭 실수는 아니었구만
That kiss isn't looking like
such a mistake now, is it?
You don't think that's
why he wants me back?
잠깐, 그것 때문에
날 또 보자는 거라고?
아무렴
Yeah!
No?
천만에
What are you talking about?
키스라니 무슨 소리야?
실수로 면접관한테 키스했는데
또 오라고 했다니 뻔하잖아
I accidentally kissed him
in the interview...
...and now he wants me back...
...because, "Let's bring back
the girl who kisses everybody!"
다시 좀 봅시다
뽀뽀쟁이 아가씨!
Come on, Rach.
그럴 리가 있나
맙소사, 날 헤픈 여자로
생각했으면 어떡하지?
What if he thinks
I'll just sleep with him?
He wants you back because
you're right for the job.
자격이 있으니까 부르겠지
글쎄, 난 모르겠다
어쩌다 그런 바보짓을 했담
Maybe. I don't know. Oh, God!
How could I be so stupid?
레이첼, 그러지 마
이 오빠가 안아줄게
Rachel, don't say that. I think
you just need a hug from Joey.
Come on. Come on.
자, 이리 와
She's back! Hot girl's back!
이쁜이가 돌아왔다!
다 풀린 건 아니지만
말이라도 고마워
Well, I'm not totally back yet,
but I appreciate it.
아니, 건너편 여자가
다시 나타났어
No. In Ross' building.
She's back!
잠깐 기다려요
금방 갈 테니까
Wait there.
I'll be over in a second.
하나, 둘, 셋... 됐다!
One, two, three....
Got it!
I gotta check out this hot girl.
이쁜이 나도 좀 봐야지
There she is!
여기 있었네
Damn it! Did you move?
망할! 너 이사했냐?
Yes.
그래
I lived with you for a while.
Then I found this place.
한동안 너희 집에 얹혀살다
이 집을 구했잖아
I'm Ross.
전 로스랍니다
네?
여기 혹시 이쁜이 없나요?
Do you happen to have
a hot girl in there?
아니, 난 혼자 산다오
No, I'm all alone.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
네, 안됐습니다
Hey, little girl.
안녕, 꼬마야
혹시 너희 엄마나 언니나
애 보는 아줌마가 예쁘니?
Is your mommy or sister or babysitter,
by any chance, a hot girl?
-Daddy!
-Later, girl!
- 아빠!
- 그럼 또 보자
Oh, man!
환장하겠네
Hot girl?
이쁜이?
Hot girl!
이쁜아!
Hi, Rachel. Come on in.
- 레이첼, 들어와요
- 안녕하세요
-It's nice to see you again.
-Thank you.
- 다시 만나서 반가워요
- 감사합니다
레이첼...
What?
네?
- 여기요...
- 왜 그러시죠?
-Excuse me?
-Yeah, let me
- 그럼 제가...
- 어허!
Okay, I see what's going on here.
Now, look...
네, 알았어요
됐으니까 들어보세요
오해하게 만든 건
제 잘못이지만
...I'm sorry if I gave you
the wrong impression.
But I am not some hussy who will
just sleep around to get ahead.
난 성공하려고 아무한테나
붙어먹는 여자가 아니에요
Even though I kissed you,
that does not give you...
에헤! 비록 제가 키스를 했지만
내게 잠자리를 요구할
권리는 없어요
...the right to demand sex from me!
I do not want this job that bad.
꼭 여기 아니라도 다닐 데는
많답니다, 좋은 하루 되세요
Good day, sir.
If you're going in there to see Mr. Zelner,
I hope you're ready to put out.
저 방에 들어갈 거면
몸바칠 준비나 해두세요
I am.
그럴 거예요
You are not gonna believe...
랄프 로렌의 그 느끼한 자식이
나한테 어떻게 한 줄 아니?
...what that sleazeball
from Ralph Lauren did to me!
Okay, that's amazing!
How did you know that?
귀신이 곡하겠네
그걸 어떻게 알았는데?
You got ink on your lip.
입술에 잉크 묻었어
언제 총 한번 만져보게
해줄 수 있어요?
What do you say, maybe,
sometime I hold your gun?
We're not supposed to do that.
글쎄요, 규정위반이라
What could happen? I mean
염려 붙들어 매고...
Yeah. I'm gonna say no.
역시 안 되겠네요
오늘 저녁 먹고
영화 보러 안 갈래?
-Do you want to see a movie tonight?
-We can't. We already have plans.
안 돼, 다른 계획이 있어
What are you doing?
뭐할 건데?
그냥 개리 아파트에서
늘 하는 거지 뭐
Well, same thing we did all day.
Just hang out at Gary's apartment.
He is so amazing.
We never left the bedroom.
정말 대단한 남자야
침실에서 산다니까
영화 재미있게 봐라
But have fun at the movie.
Well, we're not seeing a movie.
우리 영화 안 볼 거야
Then why did you ask us
if we wanted to go?
그럼 왜 우리한테
갈 거냐고 물었어?
Because I just wanted
to know what you were doing...
그냥 좀 궁금해서...
너희 오늘 뭐할지는 모르지만
갑자기 쳐들어오면 곤란하잖아
...so you wouldn't walk in
on me and Chandler...
...while we were doing it all night.
우리 밤새 할 건데
Will you excuse me?
- 잠깐만 실례할게
- 그래
- 챈들러, 잠깐 나 좀 볼까?
Chandler?
Can I see you for a second?
-We have got to beat them!
-Why?
저 두 사람을 이겨야 돼
왜?
Because Gary and Phoebe think
they're a hotter couple than us.
왜는 왜, 자기네가 우리보다
더 뜨거운 커플이래잖아
- 그래서?
So?
So we've gotta go have a lot of sex
and prove them wrong!
올라가서 열나게 해야
쟤들 기가 좀 죽지
You've got to stop this
competitive thing. It's crazy.
무슨 시합도 아니고
자기 왜 이래?
Just to impress them, you want us
to have sex over and over...
두 사람 기죽이자고
방에 올라가서
하고 또 하고 또 해?
싫긴 왜 싫어, 코트 챙겨
...and I'm saying no to this, why?
Get your coat!
내게 손을 흔든 이쁜이는
꼭 전화주세요, 조이
- 안녕하세요
- 네
실례합니다
Excuse me.
경고, 무단침입자
발견 즉시 신고 바람
You should check this out.
Tell the other tenants.
잘 봐 두셨다가
이웃들에게도 전해주세요
Apparently, he's looking
for some kind of hot girl.
무슨 이쁜이를 찾겠다고
날뛰는 녀석이니까
Who isn't?
누군 아니겠어요
I don't think we've met.
I'm Ross.
처음 뵙는 것 같은데
전 로스라고 합니다
I know. You're the guy who
wouldn't chip in for the handyman.
알아요
돈 걷을 때 협조
안 한 분이죠?
Never mind.
그만둡시다요
I actually thought it was unfair
the way everyone reacted.
아뇨, 그 사람들이
너무 심했어요
I mean, you had just moved in.
최근에 입주한 분한테
I had just moved in!
내 말이 그 말 아닙니까
감사합니다
Thank you!
Listen....
저기...
젠이에요
Jen.
- 젠?
- 네
좀 이상하게 들리겠지만...
I know this may sound a little....
나중에 커피라도 한잔할까요?
But would you want to grab
a cup of coffee sometime?
Sure, that would be nice.
네, 좋아요
My number's on there.
Give me a call.
제 전화번호예요
연락 주세요
I will give you a call.
꼭 전화할게요
-I'll see you later.
-Okay.
- 다음에 봐요
- 그래요
I forgot my paper.
신문을 잊었어요
That was amazing.
환상적이었어
Phoebe and Gary are so gonna
hear about this at dinner.
이제 피비랑 개리는
꼬리 내려야 할 걸
That was amazing.
환상적이었어
우리가 제일 뜨거워
We are the hottest, huh?
No one is hotter than we are.
누구도 우리보다 뜨겁진 못해
-We're the best.
-No, you're the best.
우리가 최고야
아니, 자기가 최고야
아냐, 자기가 최고지
-No, you're the best.
아니, 네가 최고야
I am the best.
내가 최고야
Hey, guys.
얘들아
What you been doing?
뭐하고 있었는데?
얘, 조이
Isn't that the girl who waved at you?
저 여자가 손 흔들었어?
글쎄, 시트 다 비친다
I don't know, but I can
see through your sheet.
Yeah, that's her.
그래, 맞네
이제 신경 끊었어
어쨌든 못 만날 거야
You know, it doesn't matter.
I'll never meet her.
왜?
아파트를 찾을 수가 없잖아
무슨 이쁜이 평행우주에 사나 봐
It's impossible to find her apartment!
She lives in some hot-girl
parallel universe or something.
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리야?
2층에 살잖아
She lives on the 2nd floor,
7th apartment from the left.
- 왼쪽에서 일곱 번째
- 그게 아니지
No, she lives on the 3rd floor,
8th apartment from the left.
- 3층 왼쪽에서 여덟 번째
- 아냐
No. Those first two windows,
that's the lobby.
처음 창문 두 개는 로비야
That other window is the stairway.
You've been counting wrong.
저 창문은 계단이고
잘못 봤구만 뭐
I did not know that!
Thank you, Monica.
그건 몰랐다
고맙다, 모니카
셈 잘못해서
여자 하나 놓칠 뻔했네
I almost lost another girl
because of counting!
-So you ready?
-Yeah, I'll just get my coat.
준비됐어요?
- 코트 가져올게요
- 그래요
-Could you get that?
-Sure.
- 좀 열어줄래요?
- 그러죠
뜨아!
- 조이...
- 아냐, 이럴 순 없어
No! No!
First, I would like to say
thank you for seeing me again.
우선 다시 만나겠다고
해주신 거 감사드려요
천만에요, 아무튼 이 면접은
녹화 중이니까 유념하세요
That's all right.
But I feel obligated to tell you
that this meeting is being videotaped.
좋아요
저번에 키스한 일부터
사과드리고 싶군요
Well, first, I would like to start
by apologizing for kissing you...
...and for yelling at you.
- 소리 지른 것도 그렇고
- 괜찮습니다
Fair enough.
물론 저 같은 사람은
뽑고 싶지 않으시겠죠
Now, you're probably going to hire
one of the people who did not...
...yell at you and storm out.
한바탕 퍼붓고
뛰쳐나갔으니까
And I think that's a big mistake.
And here's why.
하지만 그럼 안 되는
이유를 말씀드리죠
I made a huge fool of myself,
and I came back. That shows courage.
전 그런 바보짓을 하고도
이렇게 다시 왔어요
용기가 있다는 증거죠
When I thought you wanted sex
in exchange for this job, I said no.
오해였지만 취업을 미끼로 한
잠자리 요구도 거절했어요
That shows integrity.
그건 강직함이죠
And I was not afraid
to stand up for myself...
이렇게 제 입장을
당당히 밝히는 건
...and that shows courage.
용기라고 할 수 있죠
네, 용기 부분은
벌써 나왔지만...
Now, I know that I've
already said courage...
...but you've got to have courage.
용기는 있어야죠?
마지막으로 직장상사의
성적인 접근이 있었지만
And finally, when I thought
you were making sexual advances...
...I said no,
and I was not litigious.
거절만 했을 뿐
소송은 걸지 않았어요
So there you go!
You got courage...
자, 어떤가요
용기 있고, 강직하고
...you got integrity,
you got courage again...
또한...
용기 다시 한 번
또 소송을 일삼지도 않아요
...and not litigious.
하여간...
Look, Mr....
- 젤너입니다
- 젤너! 맞다
Zelner.
I knew that!
Oh, I knew that.
그거였지
I really, really want this job.
전 이 일을 꼭 하고 싶어요
잘할 자신도 있구요
And I think I would be
really good at it.
You know what?
- 이렇게 합시다
- 네
I may regret this...
잘하는 건지 모르지만...
...but I'll give you a shot.
기회를 주겠어요
정말이세요?
You are? Really?
- 진짜로?
- 네
감사합니다, 세상에
Thank you. Oh, God!
Would it be inappropriate
if I gave you a hug?
제가 껴안으면 곤란하겠죠?
- 네
- 알았어요
Well, how about a handshake?
그럼 악수라도 하세요
꺅! 죄송해요!
Oh, God! I'm sorry!
맙소사, 그딴 걸 만질 생각은
없었는데... 아니, 이사님을!
I did not mean to touch that!
I mean, you!
There!
네, 어쨌든 뭐...
됐군요, 감사합니다
I'm gonna leave.
Thank you very much.
가볼게요, 감사합니다
정말 감사하구요...
Hey, I'll see you Monday.
참, 월요일에 뵙죠
Are you tired?
피곤하니, 챈들러?
You better believe he's tired
after the day we had!
피곤한 게 당연하지
그렇게 무리를 했는데
If you know what I mean.
Do you know what I mean?
무슨 뜻인지 알죠?
무슨 뜻인지 알아요?
Honey, the tortilla chips
know what you mean.
자기야? 토르티야 칩도
무슨 뜻인지 알 거야
내가 준 배지 맘에 들어요?
Do you like that badge I got you?
네, 아주 멋져요
Oh, yeah, it's so cool.
10-100 상황 발생으로
본 경관은 잠시 실례하죠
Now, I gotta go.
Officer Bing's got a 10-100.
That's pee-pee.
쉬하러 간다고
Phoebe, you have a twig in your hair.
피비, 머리에 나뭇가지 붙었다
We kind of took a detour
on our way over here.
오다가 잠시 옆길로 샜거든
공원을 거닐었는데
인적이 없어서...
We were strolling through the park
and no one was around, so....
-You didn't.
-We did!
- 설마...
- 정말이야
We violated section 12,
paragraph 7 of the criminal code.
형법 12조 7항을 위반했지
The park, huh?
공원에서?
Public place.
공공장소인데?
알았어요
I hear you.
Can you excuse me for a second?
잠깐 실례할까?
Hi, Chandler.
나야, 자기
Monica, this is the men's room.
여기 남자화장실이야
Isn't it?
아닌가?
Yes, it is.
맞아
I've always found the men's bathroom
very sexual. Haven't you?
남자화장실은 너무 자극적이야
자긴 안 그래?
No.
아니...
And if I did, I don't think
we'd be going out.
그랬다면 너랑 이렇게 안 됐지
Okay, I don't want
to disappoint you...
잠깐, 자기한테는 미안하지만
저 아저씨가 불쾌할 거야
...and I really don't want to disappoint
the guy in the second stall....
Sorry, man.
송구스럽군요
But come on, this is getting ridiculous.
상황이 점점 이상해지잖아
두 사람한테 지면 안 돼
Come on, we can't let them win!
We've proved that we are hot, okay?
So why are you obsessed about this?
우리가 뜨거운 사이라는 건
증명했는데 왜 이렇게 집착해?
피비랑 개리는 지금...
Phoebe and Gary are in that...
..."can't keep their hands
off each other" phase!
공원에서 사고 칠 만큼
눈이 먼 상태라니까
So?
- 그래서?
- 그래서라니?
It makes me really sad that
we're not really there anymore.
우린 한물간 것 같아서
속상하단 말이야
Oh, is that what
this has all been about?
그래서 이러는 거야?
Wasn't it a lot more exciting
when we were...
서로를 간절히 원할 때가
훨씬 짜릿하지 않았어?
...all over each other all the time?
그래, 정말 좋았지
Yeah, that was great.
That was really great.
하지만 솔직히 말하면
난 지금이 훨씬 더 짜릿해
But the truth is, I'm more
excited about where we are now.
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 진짜?
- 그래
I've never been in a relationship
this long before.
난 누구랑 이렇게 오래
사귀어 본 적이 없어
초반의 열정이 사라져도
늘 함께 있고 싶은 사람
To get past the beginning and
still want to be around each other...
...I think that's incredible.
그게 보통 일인가?
And the fact that
this is happening with you...
이 놀라운 경험을 너와
함께 한다는 사실이
...I think that's pretty exciting.
내겐 너무 짜릿해
That's so sweet.
고마워
내가 요즘 약간 이상했지만
I know that I was acting
a little crazy...
...but I feel the same way.
나도 같은 생각이야
You know what I just realized?
방금 깨달은 건데
You just freaked out
about our relationship.
넌 우리 관계가 두려워진 거야
-I did not.
-Yes, you did!
- 그렇지 않아
- 맞아, 인정해, 겁먹었어
Admit it. You freaked out!
I freaked out a little.
- 그래, 약간 두려웠어
- 약간? 대짜로 겁먹었어
A little?
You freaked out bigtime, okay?
그걸 내가 교정했으니 역할이
뒤바뀐 거야, 이제 난 대왕이고
And I fixed it!
We have switched places.
I am the relationship king, and you
are the crazy, irrational screwup!
넌 얼이 빠져 헤매는 중생이지
And now we're back.
다시 원상복귀?
I cannot believe Ross is buying this.
로스 쟤 바보 아냐?
다행이지 뭐야
더는 못 봐주겠어
Thank God!
I can't watch him anymore.
You guys ready?
이제 영화 보러 갈까?
그래, 그리고 파멜라랑
야스민 빌려줘서 고마워
By the way, thank you for
loaning us Pamela and Yasmine.
보는 눈들은 있어갖구설랑
Man, they cannot get enough!